

IBEWUIKE NKIRUKA PRECIOUS

CUSTOMER SERVICE

DETAILS

ADDRESS:

167 Tenant Road, Aba, Abia State. Nigeria

PHONE:

08167860935

EMAIL:

ibewuikeprecious042@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH:

August 4, 1991

MARITAL STATUS:

Single

NATIONALITY:

Nigerian

SKILLS

Graphic Designer
Ms Excel Competency

EDUCATION

BSc. in Food Science and Technology Michael Okpara University of Agriculture 2012-2023

St. John's Model Secondary School, Obingwa, Abia State *2003-2009*

QUALITIES

☐ Cognitive flexibility

☐ Judgmental and decision-making skills

☐ Emotional intelligence

△ Ability to work hard under pressure with little or no supervision

☐ Good numerical, communication and presentation

INTERESTS

Travelling
Book keeping
Documentation

LANGUAGE

English Igbo

PROFILE

Supporting the management of functions in demanding cooperate environments with extensive customer's relationship experience gained at leading global organizations. I have worked across numerous business support roles including receptionist, digital marketing and distributor with the ability to meet challenging deadlines to achieve operational business goals.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Guest Service Agent 2018-2019 Water Ripples Hotel, Lekki

Lagos State

- . Responsible for guests check-ins and out
- . Responsible for Providing information pertaining to available services and facilities of hotel
- . Offer assistance to the individual needs and requests of all guests.
- . I ensure guest needs are responded to in a timely and efficient manner
- . I maintain guest confidentiality at all times
- . Responsible for guests reservations
- . Incharge of all front office functions
- . Operate phone system in, at times, a fast paced environment
- . I conduct myself in a friendly and attentive manner during all guest encounters.

Kitchen Assistant

2016-2018 Roots Restaurants and Café

Abia State

- . Maintaining cleanliness in every workstation
- . Assisting cooks with meal preparation and other duties as requested
- Maintaining accuracy of assigned tasks and customer order.
- . Storing food products safely and in line with federal and business regulations

Sales Representative 2011-2016 Nigerian Breweries Plc

Abia State

- . Deal with distributors and retailers on a regular basis, using my expertise to promote the company's products and drive sales.
- . Build friendly relationships with customers at the distribution and retailer levels
- . Have strong understanding of the beer market
- . Able to make effective marketing strategies.
- . Create a sales catalog for the company

Sales Representative 2010-2011 Reckitt Benkiser

Abia State

- Distributing samples and providing feedback for improvement
- . Following up with customers and providing guidance on product selection
- . Meeting daily targets and submitting sales reports
- . Engaging in meaningful interactions and building good relationships with customers
- . Following up with customers and providing guidance on product selection.

CERTIFICATION

- Member Nigerian Institute of Food Science and Technology
- . Acquired Industrial Training at National Root Crops Research Institute
- . Participant Annual Conference of Nigeria Association of Food Science and Technology Students
- . Participant in Mediterranic Resources Seminar on Skill Acquisition and Human Resources